<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Loan Services on UNH COMP RESOURCES</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/loan-services/index.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in Loan Services on UNH COMP RESOURCES</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language><atom:link href="//localhost:1313/loan-services/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Student&#39;s guide to loan an equipment</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/loan-services/students-guide/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/loan-services/students-guide/index.html</guid>
      <description>Student&amp;rsquo;s guide to loan an equipment COMP Department provides laptops, mobile phones and other devices like Raspberry pi, mouse, etc to the students of UNH for their academic purposes.
To loan any kind of equipment, please follow the below procedure:
Email one of the tech consultants of the COMP department requesting for loaning the equipment.
Tech consultant will get back with the availability of the equipment.
If the equipment is ready to loan, make an appointment with tech consultant.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Loaned equipment return policy</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/loan-services/covid-return-policy/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/loan-services/covid-return-policy/index.html</guid>
      <description>Loaned equipment return policy These requirements pertain to students who have chosen remote learning and do not come to campus:
The student who wants to pick up/return AES loaned equipment needs to get their COVID self-test kits. They would need to swab and drop off in the outside receptacle at least 5 days prior to when they plan to come into the building. ​OR The student who wants to pick up/return AES loaned equipment needs to meet one of the AES tech consultants outside of the building for the exchange.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>